Welcome to Limmy's Show.
Imagine you're having your lunch,
you look up
and you see that.
Some guy just staring at you.
You'd be like this.
What's he looking at?
Some guy just staring at us.
Or maybe he was staring at me because he thought I was staring at him.
Maybe we look at each other at the same time, maybe that's all it is.
No, no, no, no, he was definitely looking at me when I looked at him.
Is he still looking at me?
So you check to see.
Cool.
No, he was not staring at us.
Maybe he was looking at me, but looking at me in that way
that you know, you just look right through somebody,
and don't even know you're doing it. Aye, that's what it probably was.
Maybe we did look at each other at the same time.
Maybe... No, no, no, no, he was definitely looking at me when I looked at him,
I'm sure, because I turned around.
Caught.
Caught a dillion.
Caught sneaking back for another wee look there,
That's me made a connection with the guy now.
That's made a connection with the guy. I've got to get out of this.
I've got to get out - the guy knows I'm interested in him,
not in a sexual way, but he knows I'm thinking about him now.
He knows I'm thinking about him
but he knows that I know that he knows that...
Do you know what I mean? I've gotta break this connection.
I'm just getting on with my life, mate
Let's the two of us just move on,
you know, I'm not interested, mate,
Not interested.
(YAWNING)
I've got bigger fish to fry, mate,
bigger fish to fry.
Shit.
No. I'm not looking away this time.
I'm not looking away this time.
Nope, you started it, I'm finishing it.
I caught you, you caught me,
that's 50/50, this is it.
Me and you all the way down the line, let's go.
What are you looking at?
(CHUCKLES)
Sorry, false alarm.
Jacqueline, I've... I've had a look through your CV,
but you don't seem to have any experience in dry-cleaning.
D-do you have any?
No.
Do you have any experience of cleaning garments professionally?
Workin' in a laundrette, ironing clothes in a hotel, do you have
Look, mate, I used to be a junkie.
Alright, I'm just gonna lay my cards on the table, mate.
I used to be a junkie, I've got no experience.
I lost three year of my life
on heroin,
and another 5 year on a methadone programme
that was meant to get us off it!
Alright, but that's me clean now.
When I saw you advert in the paper for the job,
dry-cleaners, I was like, "That's a sign, that's gotta be a sign, mate."
do you know what I mean?
I thought "I've got to have this job, I've got to have this job."
I'm not looking for any special treatment, mate.
I can just promise you that I'll work my hardest
to get your clothes clean,
the same way that I worked hard to get myself clean.
Do you know what I mean?
Because that's me working for two now, mate
that's me got my daughter's back.
that's me working for two.
I need this job, mate,
I want this job. I'm working for two now, do you know what I mean?
Look, it's OK.
No, it's not OK, mate, I just
I should not have came here, I've got no experience.
I made a fool of myself.
Jacqueline.
I had...I had a relative
who found themselves in the same situation you're in
and I...and I wasn't there to help.
And I hope you don't mind the personal reasons behind my decision.
I'd like to offer you the job.
You're joking.
No.
Can you start on Monday?
Too right, mate.
Aw, that's brilliant news, what a start to the weekend, eh?
Good excuse to go out and get hammered, eh?
What?
I said it's a good excuse to go out and get hammered this weekend,
starting work on Monday!
What did you just say to me?
What's wrong?
What the fuck are you on about, "What's wrong?"
After everything I told you about me getting clean?
Pure opening my heart up to ye,
then you're like, "Ah, is that your way to get full of the smack this weekend, eh, Jacqueline?"
Get your job to fuck!
Jacqueline, I never said that!
I told you, I'm clean, alright?
Too clean for this pigsty.
He's a dirty!
American forces in Afghanistan
have came under some of the most intense fire
since the beginning of their campaign,
in a town only five miles from Kabool.
Did you hear what I said there?
I said Kabool.
Kabool.
Not Kabul.
Like we would say over here.
But Kabool.
Like they would say over there.
Impressive, isn't it?
Of course, you wouldn't hear me saying this.
The Netherlands will tonight go to the ballot box in a crucial vote
that could spell the end of the notorious red-light districts of Amshterdam
Or...
The President of America will later today attend a memorial service
at the site of the World Trade Center attacks in Nue Yoik.
Or...
A fire has broke out on a North Sea oil rig, just off the coast of
SHETLAND,
the Shetland Islands up there in Shetland.
No.
That would be silly, wouldn't it?
I only do it for places like Kabool
Here, imagine getting knocked down by an ambulance,
that would be funny, wouldn't it?
It's not.
Every day in my school,
there was always some class getting gym.
And in every class, there's always somebody who forgot their trainers.
But that never stops them from getting some excercise.
A punishment exercise!
I thought, hold on,
there's a wee gap in the market here.
So I bought a pair of sannies,
just a daft pair of slip-ons out the shops.
A hefty investment, but the higher the risk, the higher the return.
The next day, I go walking up the gym queue like that,
"Anybody looking for trainers?"
"Sannies for hire. Sannies..."
"Aye, me!"
"Me an' aw."
Mark and Colin bolt up to us at the exact same time. I was like that,
"Er, we've got a problem lads, I've only got one pair of trainers"
Mark was like that, "I shouted first."
Colin was like, "Aye, but I got to him first."
I was like, "Look, lads, I've got an idea - take a trainer each."
They were like, "Are you mental?"
I say "No, listen, they split the hall into two, don't they?"
"Yous are in two different classes, two different teachers."
"Mark, you go up to Mrs McArthur with your trainer,"
"and hit her with a sob story about how the other one fell out your bag, right?"
"Same with Mrs Ferguson, Colin."
"She normally does not fall for the missing trainers patter,"
"but having a trainer on you will lend the story a certain believability, right?"
And they were like that, "Worth a try."
I say, "Cool, 20p each."
40p, man, can you believe it?
A 40% return on my investment already!
Ąnyway, so I catches up with them at the end of the day, see how they got on.
I was dreading it, if the truth be known.
And they were like that, "Gary, you're a genius!"
I was like that, "Thank God."
And that was the end of that.
No, it was not.
Because a couple of days later,
there's me in the middle of serving a customer
and I get a hand slapped on my shoulder.
Turns around and there's Mark and Colin with pure scowls on their faces.
They were like that, "We want our money back, it didn't work."
I was like that, "Aye, it did."
They were like that, "No, it didn't."
They tells us they got pulled out their classroom and their teachers said to them
"Boys, we've just had a conversation about how two of our pupils,"
"in the exact same gym hall,"
"on the exact same day,"
"managed to lose the exact same sandshoe."
"Can you explain why that is?"
I was like that, "Aw, you are joking!"
They were like that, "No, 500 lines each, it's no joke, so gie's out money back."
I was like that, "No chance!"
"I provided yous with a solution to your problem in that moment in time,"
"the problem being imminent punny eccies."
"You knew the risks, you accepted the deal, no refund."
Two of them started squaring up to me like that,
"Don't wan't to hear it, Gary. Money, now."
I was like that, "It's came to this, then, has it?
And I chucked their money on the deck. Told them not to come back.
And they were like that, "So what?"
So what? See they two?
They're not getting a lend of a pair of trainers for the rest of their lives.
No hauners in any fights.
No dragging them out of the grog pit.
Nothing. That's them on themselves.
Right, ta.
♪ Let's dance ♪
♪ For fear your grace should fall ♪
♪ For fear tonight is all ♪
♪ Let's sway ♪
♪ You could look into my eyes ♪
♪ Under the moonlight ♪
♪ The serious moonlight ♪
We've got to save the planet.
That's what they say.
Our planet is dying.
Good.
Don't want to save the planet.
Because the reason for saving the planet
is so it can be enjoyed by future generations in't it?
But what if I hate them?
Because here we've got the next generation right here.
Look.
He looks like his trousers have fell down.
See in my day, see if you looked like that, it would be because
your trousers have fell down.
That's the sort of thing you used to run up behind people and do to them.
I hate him.
And as for generations to come, people 500 years from now,
I have not even met them and I hate them already.
You should as well because they will be looking back to this day and age
and they'll be laughing at us.
Calling us barbarians, pure giving us a hard time.
Why would you want to leave them a beautiful planet that's in perfect nick?
I could not bear the thought of they people on my planet,
pure livin' it up, no way!
You know what the saddest thing is?
We won't be there to laugh back at them, to give them a hard time
But we can get the planet
to give them a hard time on our behalf.
By destroying it.
By leaving them a planet so ravaged
that they just need to step out into the sunlight and their skin will fall off.
And in that small way,
even though we'll be dead.,
we'll have lived on
through dear old Mother Earth.
So cheer up.
It's not the end of the world.
Severe floods in North Wales have left almost 700 people homeless,
many without adequate food or shelter.
Did you see that?
I said,
700 people homeless.
Watch how I shake my head.
Watch how I wave my hands.
700 people homeless.
That's a little trick I use in order to help you know
that what I just told you is
bad news.
Sorry, sorry to interrupt the show, folks, I've got an idea.
It's a wee trick we can play on all the folks not watching
the show the night, right?
What it is is, see when you're out and about
see if you see a stone on the ground,
pick it up, and on the ground
draw an arrow.
See if you can be bothered, keep it with you,
take it with you, and wherever you go, every now and again...
another arrow on the ground.
If enough of us do it, your arrows will lead to somebody else's arrows
that will lead to somebody else's.
Arrows that lead to arrows that lead to arrows.
Let's send these bastards everywhere.
(AUDIENCE TITTERING)
(MENACING LAUGHTER)
You'll never catch me!
I'm your worsest nightmare!
(SCREAMING)
Imagine it.
Imagine seeing your doppelganger.
Imagine seeing somebody who's identical to you in every way.
How mental would that be, eh?
Aye, well, come here.
Dogs.
In the '70s, you had your Alsatian, you know, your German shepherd.
And in the '80s, you had your Doberman,
you know, your Doberman pinscher
In the late '80s and '90s, you had your Rottweiler.
And now it's your bull terrier,
your Staffordshire bull terrier,
pit bull terrier,
it's just totally out of control, innit?
So what the Government did
and this was a while back, you will not remember this -
was they got in touch with the Kennel Club,
and they said, "No more."
"If you breed any more of these dangerous dogs,"
"then we're not letting you breed any."
And the Kennel Club said,
"Are you sure about that?"
And see, after a moment's thought,
the Government backed down,
because they knew they could ban every kind of breed of dog that there is
they could not ban dogs altogether.
Because what people would end up doing
is they would swap out their old dogs
for a breed of dog
that was not a breed of dog.
And do you know what that is?
The wolf.
Picture one of these swines with a wolf.
AAAOOOO!
AAOOOOO!
AOOOOOOOOOOOOooooo!
Computer,
locate all global instances of men wearing low-slung denims.
Approximately 102 million instances worldwide.
Select 3 at random that are within CCTV range.
Selected.
On screen.
Computer, gie's some controls.
Computer, synchronise controls with all global instances of low-slung denims.
Computer, activate microphone.
Activated
Pull up your trousers!
You're watching Adventure Call.
My name is Falconhoof.
And I will be your guide on your quest.
Greetings, line six, what is your name, traveller?
Ped!
Greetings, Ped. Are you ready to begin your quest?
No, I'm not Ped. You're Ped!
What is your name, traveller?
It's Stu.
Are you ready to begin your quest?
You don't remember me, don't you now?
Have you been on Adventure Call before, Stu?
Ped, it's Stu.
Stuart Richmond from school, mind.
Oh, Stu, Stu.
Greetings. Greetings, old friend.
Would you like to begin your quest?
Aye, on you go. I'm only on to say hello, really.
You are at the bottom of a well.
Mad Ped.
There is a-
Sorry, traveller?
No I was just saying "Mad Ped".
I cannot believe you're on the telly.
It was Graham who told us.
I bumped into him at the Horseshoe
and I was like that, "What's Mad Ped up to nowadays?"
He says you're on the telly doing some daft quiz show.
I was like that, "That madman?!"
How'd you land on your feet anyway, ya maddy?
There is a...
To your east is a loose brick in the wall of the well
There is...
Sorry, Ped, I didn't mean to embarrass you, mate.
It's OK, traveller, but I must ask you to believe in the adventure otherwise it will not be true.
I am-I am Falconhoof,
if you know what I mean?
Aye, no bother, mate, I'm just on to say hello.
Stacey says hello and all by the way.
Right, all the best, Ped.
I'll maybe catch up with you later, right.
Maybe if you're heading to the-
Stacey?
Stacey that I...
Stacey that I used to...?
Aye, Stacey. I told her what Graham said,
that you've got this quiz show
she's really happy for you. She still really likes you, mate.
Really?
Aye, likes you a lot, mate.
And are you seeing Stacey?
Is she your travelling partner, if you like?
No, no, no, I'm not going out with her, mate.
Don't worry, don't worry.
That's...
Just shagging her now and then,
but no, I'm not going out with her.
So feel free to batter in any time, mate.
I see. Goodbye, traveller.
See ya, Ped. Aye, batter in.
Just now on a Wednesday, alright?
Let's take another call.
See if you can escape the well.
You see, the problem with being on a bus is
you sometimes get this overwhelming urge
to just blurt something out and make a complete fool of yourself, don't you?
AAAAAAAAAAAGH!
AAAAAAAAAAH!
HAHAHAHAA HA!
NOOOOOOOO!
NOOOOOO!
The Prime minister has warned that a full economic recovery could take...
"longer than expected".
and that the Government borrowing may increase in years to come.
Did you see what I did there?
When I said,
"longer than expected",
I looked down at the piece of paper, didn't I?
That's because it was a quote.
I read off the Autocue and it said...
I look down to my quote sheet...
one, two, three, four, five
"longer than expected".
Pretty neat, huh?
We're all thinking about each other, aren't we?
Aye.
Thought so.
I want you inside me, hen.
(SCREAMING)
Fuckin',
I don't work, right?
And people think that makes your head go to pot.
But I spot things.
I think about things that other people haven't got the time for.
Like,
there was this advert on the telly,
about four in the morning
for one of they CD collections.
And the song that was playing was that
I Wanna Know What Love Is by Foreigner.
And it had the names of all these other songs coming up,
like, Sheena Easton, Modern Girl
and Love Bites by Def Leppard.
And they were in white.
Then,
I Wanna Know What Love Is by Foreigner popped up,
but that was in yellow.
And I was like that,
"Right, so if the words are in yellow,"
"that means that's the song that's playing. Cool."
Then the song changed to Crockett's Theme
by Jan Hammer.
And I was like that,
"Right, so soon we'll be seeing a wee 'Jan Hammer', Crockett's Theme in yellow,"
"I get it now."
Lionel Ritchie, Hello.
That was in white.
Right.
Here I Go Again, Whitesnake
That was in white and all. Cool.
Guess what comes up in yellow.
You guessed it
Circle in the Sand by Belinda Carlisle. I was like that...
What?
Then the song came on.
But no mention of Jan Hammer, not once.
People are like that,
"Dee Dee, you must be going braindead, just sitting about doing fuck-all all day."
But I must have been the only guy that spotted that, man.
Do you want to go faster?
Then screeeeeam!
Get on the outside, the left side's the best side.
Scream if you want to go faster!
Scream, scream, scream!
I'd like to move on now,
and talk about your first real taste of the West End stage environment.
At the age of 19,
you were thrust into the lead role of Hamlet.
A very young age to take on such a prominent role,
usually reserved for actors of around twice the age.
I mean,
that must have been a very proud achievement for you.
Sure.
Previous to myself playing Hamlet,
it was generally regarded as a...
as a role for 30-year-olds, 40-year-olds,
but
Stuart Havish of the Windsor Theatre
who was the director of the Windsor Theatre at the time, he gave me my big break,
as it were, and I...
I haven't looked back since.
So it's, it's, it's, it's, it's, it's, it's, it's, it's, it's, it's, it's,
tis, tis, tis, tis, tis, tis, tis, tis, tis,
tis, tis, tis, tis, tis, tis, tis, tis, tis, tis, tis,
tis, tis, tis, tis, tis, tis, tis, tis, tis, tis, tis, tis, tis, tis, tis, tis,
great, yeah, very proud achievement
Well, ladies and gentlemen, that's the end of the show.
Hope you've enjoyed it.
See you later.
SUBS BY f7cjo HERBU GOMEZ
Bye-bye.