Welcome to Limmy's Show.
Imagine you were in a record shop and you saw that.
You'd be like this.
Wouldn't you?
Welcome back to Adventure Call,
where we rejoin Stevie on line two.
All right, Falconhoof?
Do you realise, Stevie, that you are on the verge of being the first traveller
to find the Black Ruby of Voldesade?
Aye. Can we just get on with it, mate?
That's half an hour I've been playing this, come on.
Very well.
As you recall, we are in a marble hallway.
In the centre is a statue of Hermes.
To the east is a tunnel of no return.
Right.
And to the west is a maze.
Kiss feet of Hermes.
You kiss the feet of Hermes.
A pair of winged sandals appears next to-
Yes! Get winged sandals!
I told you, didn't I?!
I must warn you again, Stevie, that I cannot receive your instructions
until I have finished describing the environment to the viewers at home.
Right, well, hurry up, then!
A pair of winged sandals appear next to the feet of Hermes.
What would you like to do?
Enter tunnel.
Are you sure?
Move!
You're stalling for time.
Aye, they try to squeeze every penny out of you.
Very well.
The tunnel takes you north.
As you exit, it vanishes behind you.
You now stand before the Chasm of Fire.
To the east is a maze.
To the north, at the other side of the Chasm
is...
the Black Ruby of Voldesade.
YES! Jump the Chasm.
Be careful. The chasm cannot be jumped by mere mortals.
Aye, but I'm not a mere mortal.
I'm wearing the winged sandals, so just jump.
You are not.
I'm not what?
You are not wearing the winged sandals.
How not?
You do not have them.
Aye, I do.
You do not.
Well, where are they?
They are next to the feet of Hermes.
What are they doing there?
I told you to get them, I told you I wanted to wear them.
You did not.
Aye, I did!
No, you didn't. No, you did not.
You gave me the instructions to get the the winged sandals while
I was describing the surroundings,
and I made it clear that-
No.
No, no, no, mate.
That is petty, that is petty.
That is not petty. I advised you that I
could not receive your instructions until-
But you heard me!
You actually heard me tell you to get the winged sandals,
and you left them behind without warning me,
just to prove a point!
I did warn you, I did warn you.
No, look, here's what we're gonna do, right?
You could enter the maze to return to the marble hallway.
Aye, right, and add another 50 quid to my phone bill?
No, mate, here's what's gonna happen, are you listening?
Yes.
I'm going to jump over the Chasm of Fire
I'm gonna reach the other side and I'm going to get that Black Rub-
You will not.
I'd better, mate!
I'm gonna get to the other side, and I'm going to get that Black Ruby, and I'm going to get my two grand.
You will not make it, traveller.
I'd better, mate!
I'm warning you. Jump the Chasm.
You will need the winged sandals.
I've got them! I told you to get them, I've got them.
Now, jump the Chasm!
Traveller...
Jump the Chasm!
Okay, you jump the Chasm.
You make a pitiful jump into the flames.
Noooo! You'd better not have, mate!
You are burnt to a cinder.
You are dead.
No! You're dead, mate, you're dead!
You've just cost me two grand! You are a dead man.
I'm going to find out where you drink and you're a fu-
We're ready to take another caller.
My name is Falconhoof,
and I will be a guide on your quest.
Will you be my da'?
(SCREAMING)
You know what I hate?
I hate that when I want crisps
I get chips.
When I want fish and chips
they come with fries.
I hate that the flats are now called apartments.
I hate that sweets are now called candy.
And I hate that instead of instead of nipping out to the shops,
you nip out to the convenience store.
I hate it.
I hate when we use American words
in place of words that we've already got for their words.
Just because it's cool.
Well, tell me, is this cool?
There you've got an old woman,
and she's needing her prescription for her chronic back pain
and her bad heart.
But she's not getting it,
because she's looking for her chemist,
the same chemist she's been going to for the last 30 year.
But she cannot find it,
because there in its place is...
Lloydspharmacy.
Lloydspharmacy! Some trendy cocktail bar,
some trendy clothes shop called Lloydspharmacy.
Lloydspharmacy, one word.
And she's heading up the road, confused,
thinking she's losing her marbles,
and she's going to her bed with her back killing her,
and she's dying in her fucking sleep!
No, that's not cool,
because that's our granny.
That's your granny.
That's anybody's granny!
(APPLAUSE)
Whooo!
Hey!
Shit!
♪ I wanna have dinner with Gershwin ♪
You want to have dinner with Gershwin?
The composer, George Gershwin?
He's been dead for about 70 years. What are you going to do?
Just...
dig his corpse up and stick it at the end of your dinner table?
♪ I want to watch Rembrandt sketch ♪
You want to watch Rembrandt sketch?
He wouldn't let you.
Artists are notorious for not letting anybody see their work before it's finished, so...
♪ I want to talk theory with Curie ♪
Curie?
Marie Curie?
You want to talk about the theory of radioactivity with Marie Curie?
Donna, you wouldn't have a clue what she was on about.
Even if you could speak Polish.
♪ Ooh, impossible, I guess ♪
You said it.
(DISTANT VOICES)
(THEY SPEAK MOCK LATIN)
What's goin' on here, like?
We need to talk.
What about?
I want to split up.
Split up?
What for?
I'm fed up. Really fed up.
I've been fed up for years.
We don't go out, we don't do anything.
I don't understand, this is totally out of the blue.
I thought we were getting on. What's happened?
Nothing's happened, that's what's wrong.
I feel like...
I feel like I'm...
We're no'...
We're no' what? What's wrong?
Oh, I don't know.
I'm talking shite, just forget it.
Is everything all right?
Aye.
Hello, reception.
Cathy, have the police called today?
No.
Have they been in the building at any point?
Not that I'm aware of. Are you expecting them?
No, no, not at all, just checking, thank you.
Okay.
That's no call for complacency, the police could walk in the door at any moment,
and you don't have a story.
"Hello, officer, how can I help you?"
"Er, Mr. Mulvaney, do you reside anywhere...
near the Drumchapel area of Glasgow?"
"Drumchapel? Nowhere near it, fortunately. Er, why?"
"Ah, well, eh, last night an incident occurred between the hours of..."
"I see, well, that's, er,
that's quite depressing"
"It's incidents like that that give Drumchapel a bad name."
"I hope you catch the chap."
"Er, well, Mr. Mulvaney, we actually have reason to believe that it was you who..."
"Me?!"
"Are you joking?"
"Officer, I'm 62 years of age."
"Why on earth would I...
vandalise a bus shelter?"
"Er, well,
written on the bus shelter was a name and it said..."
"But there must be thousands of Mulvaneys out there. What makes you think it was this one?"
Oh, that's good, that was...
Cath-
"And if I was to write my name on a bus shelter, officer, I don't think I'd use a lighter."
Cathy?
Mr. McMillan rang to say that the accounts are ready for you now.
Oh, that's great.
And Cathy, if the police do arrive,
you can just send them right on in.
No bother.
"But officer, there must be thousands of Mulvaneys out there."
Oh, that's goooood.
There are girls in your area!
Girls in your area!
Right here, right now!
Girls!
Oh, sometimes it's just a bit too...
Pow! Pow!
Do you know what I mean?
All right, I tell you what we're gonna do, we're gonna get a divorce.
For what you did to me, we're gonna get a divorce,
I'm gonna get the kids, and I'm gonna bring them up to hate you!
Computer.
Locate this man.
Located.
On screen.
Computer, activate the teleportation portal.
Activated.
Computer, position the destination portal just behind that lassie's arse, eh?
Positioned.
Oh!
No, this is childish.
This is childish.
If you're still using a phone box
in this day and age,
then you're either a drug addict
or a drug dealer
or something like that.
Fact!
She's here.
Dance for me.
That's it. Do your little turn.
Yeah, that's it.
You got it.
You got it good!
Yeah.
Yeah. Do your little turn.
Dance, dance, dance!
Yo, daddy-o.
Oh!
Who, me?
No, him.
Aye, these blondes.
You know, these blond lassies.
That's all you hear about.
A leggy blonde, a sexy blonde, innit?
Aye.
Aye, well, here's what they don't tell you.
See when one of them comes over here from Sweden,
because that's where they all come from,
they cannot believe their luck.
All of a sudden everybody wants their wicked way with them.
Whereas back home,
they don't get a second look.
Do you want to know why that is?
Why?
Because, see in Sweden,
do you know what a blonde is?
What?
A ginger.
Blondes are ginger.
Shit!
Fucking...
I was in my kitchen, right?
Checking to see if my T-shirt was dry, right?
And I just burst out laughing.
Because on the label of my T-shirt,
It said "George"
because I got it from Asda.
And it was if, every time I leave the kitchen,
everything in the kitchen springs to life.
Like, Toy Story
And his name's George
I was pissing myself.
Just imagine the slaggin' he must get from the rest of the kitchen,
like that, fuckin'...
♪ Georgie Porgie, pudding and pie ♪
♪ Kissed the girls and made them cry. ♪
But then I thought, "Naw, maybe no'."
Don't get me wrong, I've got no doubt that his nickname's Georgie Porgie,
but it might be one of their nicknames that they don't dare call him to his face,
like Joe Bananas.
Because if you ever called Joe Bananas
"Joe Bananas",
he'd fucking go bananas.
Well, maybe if you call Georgie Porgie
"Georgie Porgie",
he fucking goes bananas.
But then I thought "No, maybe not."
Because it's not as if a T-shirt's going to be the hard man of the kitchen.
That would probably be...
the kitchen knife.
But then I thought, "No, hold on."
Kitchen knife in a fight against...
the frying pan.
Frying pan would win.
Kitchen knife in a fight against the chopping board.
Chopping board would win.
Chopping board wouldn't even feel it.
Chopping boards are made to not give a fuck about kitchen knives.
Kitchen knife in a fight against me?
Aye, the kitchen knife would win then.
But I'm the only one in the kitchen the kitchen knife would win against.
And I just thought that I bet the rest of the kitchen are onto that
and pure take the piss out the kitchen knife, bullying it, grog on it.
And that got me worried.
Because it reminded me of these schoolboys you get in America that get bullied.
But then they come into school one day
and kill everybody.
And because I'm the only one in the kitchen the kitchen knife can kill,
aye, that got me worried.
So I just thought "Look, you've came in, you've checked your T-shirt,"
"it's not dry yet, just get out and leave them to it."
No, I'm not saying that my kitchen actually does come to life when I leave, right?
I'm not mental or anything.
But see as I was walking out,
seeing my frying pan,
I gave it a wee dunt.
I gave it a wee dunt in front of the kitchen knife.
Just in case.
One.
Two.
Three.
Pick a number.
If you picked two...
Square.
Circle.
Triangle.
Pick a shape.
If you picked triangle...
Red.
Green.
Blue.
Pick a color.
If you picked red,
you're out.
If you picked blue, you're out.
But if you picked green...
All right, folks, how are you doing?
Aye, great to be here. Thank you.
Oh, aye, look at this place... Yes, er...
How are you doing, sir, all right?
How are you doing? What's your name?
Aye. What do you do, mate?
You're a...? You're a...?
Oooh! Ooooh! Ooooh! Whoooo!
Only kidding, mate. Thanks for coming.
Aye.
What about you, mate? What's your name?
What do you do?
You're a...?
Oh, you're joking! Ye'll be able to...
I'm only kidding.
So, who's this?
Is that yo-Are you two together, aye?
That wee...?
Ooooooh! I'm onl-I'm only kidding.
No, seriously, it's good to be here. Absolutely fantastic.
I'll be honest with you, I've got...
I know. One, two, three... Right. Oh, right!
Aye, but... So there I was the other day... So I walks in.
Guy goes like that, you know...
So I says, er, "I don't know..."
Says, "Are you...?"
I says, "Who, me?"
Thank you very much! Good night.
Ahhhhhhhhhh.
Are you finished in here?
What?
Aye, that's me finished.
I know what you're thinking, lads.
And I used to thing the exact same thing myself.
Why does every statue I see seem to have a bigger cock than me?
Until I realised why.
Look.
No pubes.
Now, it doesn't bother me at all.
Ah!
Well, ladies and gents, that's the end of the show.
Thanks for watching.
But before you go, I'd like to leave you with a wee story
about how my auntie
lost her sight.
She was about eight years old.
And she was sneaking about her mom's bedroom,
just trying on her make-up, and trying on her high heels,
usual stuff that wee lassies do.
And she came across her mom's contact lenses.
Now, back in their days, contact lenses were made of glass.
Really dangerous to wear, especially for a wee lassie.
But, my auntie didn't know that.
So what she did was, she put this lens, this piece of glass, on her eye.
A piece of glass, it was the wrong size, wrong shape for her eyeball.
Then she blinked.
And what actually happened was - and this is horrible -
what actually happened was...
Look at you.
You'd love to know, wouldn't you?
You'd love to know.
Here's me about to tell you how
a wee lassie lost her sight.
after putting a bit of glass in her eye.
And there's you,
perched on the edge of your seat, like that,
"Oh, yes, cannot wait to find out what happens next!"
"Do continue, please, do go on."
You know what the thing is, and all?
I just made it up. Just...
I don't know.
What's wrong with us?
End of the show.
No. Music off. Get...
SUBBED BY F7CJO FOR THE KING
What's wrong with us?