Welcome to Limmy's Show.
Imagine you just started following somebody.
Fuck.
Can I help you?
No, I'm just... I'm just looking...
I'm just looking.
Sure. If you need a wee hand, just give me a shout.
Awright.
I'd say we've got to go on holiday again, the four of us, even if it's just for a weekend.
That was some laugh, wasn't it?
But, that reminds me.
You know me and Rachel are
getting married next year?
Mhm.
Well, I was wondering if... if you fancied being my best man.
Really?
Aye. Look, if you're not up for it, it's fine.
No, no, it's not that. Is it not usually your brother that's supposed to be your best man?
Aye, the tradition is you get your brother,
but see over the last few years,
you've been more like a brother to me than he has.
Seriously I love my brother, but you and me,
we're joined at the hip. We're like Ant and Dec.
No, you've always been there to help.
You've... You're always there to listen.
I mean, I can tell you anything.
You know I've always had trouble opening up, trusting people.
It's because of the way my dad was, you know all that.
Oh, listen, mate, I'd be honoured.
Pure bubbling here.
Right, listen, I've got a secret to tell you.
What?
It's just something I want to get cleared out the way, I never thought we'd be pals like this,
but now you've asked me to be your best man,
I just thought I'd come clean, get it out of the way.
What, have you been knocking money out my wallet?
No. It's nothing really, it's...
Right.
Right, you'll never believe how we first met.
Aye, in the shop.
Well, I suppose it was. But, eh, right...
Do you know for the first couple of years we were pals,
I was effectively stalking you.
How do I explain?
Right, you know when I started working at your work?
Aye.
I only took that job...
to get closer to you.
That's weird as fuck.
I cannot even look at you when you're saying that.
Imagine you did do that.
It's true!
I just decided one day I was going to pick somebody at random, get...
right into their life, and that was you.
Like, you gave a pound to a beggar, I think it was, and, er,
then you were looking in a shop window, nearly ran right into you there.
And then I followed you around the corner you went into your work.
And I followed you in and I applied for the job, and that was that.
I remember that.
I remember giving a pound to a homeless guy.
But... how do you know that?
Because I followed you!
Who are you?
Look, who's being weird now, mate?
C'mon, it's me.
G-Get away from me!
Who are you?
This...
The whole... the whole... so... the whole...
so the whole thing's a lie?
The whole thing's a lie. My dad...
My dad... the whole thing's... the whole thing's...
the whole thing's...
A lie... a lie...
And he went on to have a complete nervous breakdown,
and he threw himself off the Kelvin Bridge.
My name's Jacqueline McCafferty.
I lost three years of my life on heroin,
and another five years on a methadone programme that was meant to get us off it.
Got my daughter taken off us, the lot.
But now that I've got her back, I'm going to make sure she gets the family she never got.
Oh, splendid, mate, splendid.
Jacqueline, is it?
Aye, and this is my daughter.
Hiya.
So, er, are you happy with it?
Oh, more than happy, mate. More than happy.
Mum, what is this?
The man's gonna take a photie
and he's gonna use his computer to make it look like we're on holiday.
The way we would have been, hen, if I wasn't away being so stupid!
But I'm back now. Back and better than before
and better than that lot out there looking down their noses.
We're going to hang some pictures on the wall, hen, starting with this one, and I'm gonna make sure
McCafferty!
Jacqueline McCafferty!
You're barred.
Is this a fucking wind-up?
No. You're barred out this supermarket for shoplifting
and you know that, Jacqueline.
No, I don't. Mate, it's not me. I don't care what you say.
I'm not having this conversation with you.
I remember your face. Your name's Jacqueline McCafferty,
and I'm not suprised you cannot remember mine,
after the state you were in court.
Out!
Mate, gonna gie's a break?
I'm clean. Awright?
I'm fuckin' clean.
I've booked this studio time here.
I just want a photie of my daughter.
Can I not just get a photie of my daughter?
I'm fuckin' clean!
Awright, get your photograph taken and then get out.
Okay, just pick up where we left off?
Nice big smiles.
I try.
I try to put my past behind me,
but there on the wall is my daughter,
looking right into its eyes.
Do you want to just bin it?
No, Mum! Promise me you'll never bin it.
I promise.
It'll never let me go.
No, sorry, sorry, sorry.
Why are we here?
Why are we here? The folk with the laptops, why are we here?
What do you mean?
Because...
I've came in here to use the Wi-Fi
when I've got Wi-Fi in the house.
I only stay around the corner and I know yous do and all, because I've seen you here before,
I've seen you here before, I've seen you here before.
I'm paying two pounds for a cup of tea!
Two pounds for a cup of hot water and a tea bag,
just so that I can use the Wi-Fi connection when I'm already paying for one!
Seriously, why are we here?
It's nice to get out.
What?
But we're not out.
We're in.
This may as well be your house.
The only difference being, in this house,
you've got no control over the music,
so you got to put up with that shite.
You've got a living room full of complete strangers who don't want to speak to you
and over there behind the counter you've got a flatmate who'll make you a cup of tea any time you want,
as long as you slip him a couple of quid a pop!
Seriously, why are we here?
It's up my shiter.
Urgh!
Thank you. Um, yeah. I just want to ask this question. Um.
I'm quite suprised it hasn't came up during the debate so far, considering it's about war.
Um...
does the panel think that a person has the right...
to kill another person?
Well, thank you for giving me probably the most difficult question of the night.
And it is a difficult question, does someone have the right to take another person's life? Well,
the answer to that differs greatly, depending on...
the situation. For example,
if you were in a kill-or-be-killed situation,
the answer is very different than if you were a serial killer.
You know, does someone have the right, to kill another person?
Now, a few things you have to
Excuse me, sorry, sorry, sorry
I suppose I'm not making myself clear here. I'm only asking for a yes or no.
Sure, sure, I totally understand, but it is a difficult question and it requires an answer that
Yeah, just a yes or no will suffice. Um...
Yeah, like I said, I completely understand, but it isn't as simple as a
yes or no, you know. We have to ask
How simple do you want it? Yes or no.
Well, to answer your question, if I may be allowed to answer your question,
you're asking me to, you know... does someone have the right to
take another person's life?
And I'm trying to say, well, you know, the answer
differs greatly, depending on
No, no, no, no, no, no. Yes or no? Yes or no?
Yes or no? You cannot even answer yes or no!
Sure. I completely understand but it isn't as simple as
I'm just asking for a yes or no. Do you think someone has the right to kill another person, yes or no?
Yes or no?
Look, I am trying to answer you, but you're asking me to give you a yes or no.
It is very difficult to give a yes or no to that type of question.
How is it a difficult question? I'm only asking for a yes or no.
I know, but it isn't as simple, it's...
The answer can't be as black and white as
No, no, no. Yes or no?
Yes or no?
Okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay.
If you were in the circumstance
Yes or no?
Yes-you cannot even answer yes or no!
What do you want me to say? Do you want me to just say yes?
Do you want me to just say...
Hm? Huh? What? Hm? Huh?
I'll kill you, you wank.
Topper, eh?
Topper.
Computer.
Select 10% of all pairs of socks worldwide.
Selected.
Target one sock from each pair.
Targets locked.
Fire.
Complete.
What?!
What!
What is it?
It's as if...
It's as if what?
Aw, nothing.
Sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, folks.
I need to have a word with you.
It's came to my attention that some of yous watching the show right now...
think my show...
is crap.
It's not crap.
The reason why you think it's crap isn't because it's not funny.
No, no, no, no, no.
It's because you're just thinking about it too much.
I mean...
picture a dog
in the back seat of a motor.
going down a motorway at 70 miles an hour.
Now, a dog doesn't worry itself about how everything works,
a dog doesn't go like that, "You know, what's this all about?"
"What's this all about? This cannot be possible!"
"What does this all mean?"
"How can we be going this fast down this motorway?
"This thing hasn't even got legs! How does it all work?"
The dog doesn't question the physics of what's going on around it.
It simply sticks its head out the window
and enjoys the sensation of that 70-miles-an-hour wind in its face,
the way it makes its ears flap about,
the way it makes it feel like it's flying down the street.
And how is a dog able to be chilled out about everything?
Because it doesn't think about everything so much!
Be like the dog.
♪ And it's too late, baby ♪
♪ Now it's too late... ♪
Is that right, Dina?
Is it too late, aye?
Check this out.
(MIMING OUT OF SYNC)
♪ There will be good times waiting for me and you ♪
Again.
(MIMING OUT OF SYNC)
♪ There will be good times ♪
Here, Dina,
looks like if there's anybody that's too late around here, it's you!
Are you awright?
Aye. I could have got electrocuted.
That looks nasty.
You got off lightly. You could have been electrocuted.
That's what I was just saying there.
So there's me chilling out in the playground, letting my lunch settle.
Steg bolts up to me, and he's like that,
"Gary, Gary, you don't know what a dildo is."
I was like that, "Aye, I do."
Steg was like that, "Prove it!"
I was like that, "Steven, Steven, don't try to teach your granny to suck eggs, mate."
Steg was like that, "What?"
So I pointed out to him that I was well aware that Big Ramey
was making a laughing stock of anybody who didn't know what a dildo was.
And if Steg wanted the knowledge to avoid such a fate, it would cost him.
Steg says, "How much?"
I says, "What you got?"
He says, "All I've got is cola cubes."
I says, "Give me four."
And he starts getting them out of his bag.
I says, "You know, Steg, he's not just asking people what a dildo is."
Steg's like that, "He's not?"
I was like that, "No, sometimes he's asking people what a johnny bag's used for."
"Sometime's he's asking what VD is. I'm not sure if you're covered."
He was like that, "Does that cover it?"
I was like that, "Tch, only seven?"
"I'll tell you what, I'll give you two for seven."
He was like that, "But, Gary, what if he asks me the one I don't know?"
"What two should I pick?"
I says, "I don't want that on ma heid, that's your decision."
"And you better make it quick, because here comes Ramey."
Steg was like that, "Shit! Em, well, VD, never heard of VD."
"Dildo, I've heard a few rumors so I might know what that is."
"Johnny bag, never heard of that either. So..."
"it's VD and johnny bag."
I was like that, "Final answer?"
He was like that, "Final answer."
So I tells him. And he was like that,
"That's disgusting!"
"What's disgusting?"
Big Ramey turns up.
Steg's like that, "Nothing."
Ramey's like that, "Wee man."
Steg's like that, "What?"
Here it was, the moment of truth.
And Ramey goes,
"What's a dildo?"
I was like that, "Oh no!"
And Steg was no doubt thinking the exact same thing.
But he gave it his best shot.
He looked Ramey square in the face and said,
"A dildo is when a lassie does a shite, and it's hanging out of her arse and it looks like a cock."
The place erupted with laughter, man.
Everybody, even the wee Primary ones were like that,
"♪ You don't know what a dildo is! ♪"
Couldn't help laughing myself.
Shouldn't laugh, though.
Because he had to change school.
Good boy, and all.
I went and done the toilet on somebody up the town.
Gie's more vinegar.
Excuse me,
is there a toilet in here?
You're a toilet!
Excuse me,
is there a toilet in here?
There is, but it's not working, sorry.
Oh, right, thanks.
You're a toilet!
Argh, eugh!
Eugh! Oh no!
Oh no! Oh no!
Eugh! Eugh! Eugh!
Here!
You're a toilet!
Here.
Imagine you woke up one morning
and you were like this...
Aaaargh!
Heavy duty.
Doesn't bear thinking about it, does it not?
Life, eh?
Life.
Let me tell you about life.
This here represents you in your prime.
Represents you looking good and feeling good.
You might not be the best-looking person in the room, but when you look at yourself in the mirror,
you think, "You know what,"
"I'm not bad."
"I'm not bad at all."
You see this?
This represents life.
That's life.
And they're like that
every
single
night.
Fuckin',
I was watching GMTV, right?
And I thought, "Right, you, time for you to get your kip, c'mon."
"It was a good night of telly and that, but c'mon, eight in the morning,"
"beyond a joke, man."
Just ready to switch the thing off,
but then this advert came on for some bacteria yoghurt thing,
and I thought, "Aye, that looks nice, that."
Bird goes like that...
"Great-tasting new yoghurt from Danone fights to restore the natural good bacteria in your system."
I was like that, "Aye, awright."
Goes to switch it off,
but then at the end, this wee tune goes like that,
"♪ Nnn, Da-nun. ♪"
I was like that, "I did not hear that, man,"
do you know what I mean?
Because it sounded like the talking bird said, "New from Da-none"
But the singing bird said it like, "Da-nun",
like this
"♪ Nnn, Da-nun ♪"
Must have imagined it, they don't make mistakes like that, know?
So I got myself comfy again.
Decided I was not heading to my scratcher until we had this thing sorted out.
Waited for the adverts to come up again.
No show.
Until eventually...
Gets to the end of Loose Women.
Pure half one in the afternoon, up for 24 hours.
practically propping my eyelids open with matchsticks,
starting to forget what I was up for.
Bingo.
Tunes into it, and the bird goes like that,
"Great-tasting new yoghurt from..."
"Da-none."
I was like that, "Right, cool, Da-none"
"That one's Da-none."
But now for the sucker punch.
Bird goes like that,
"♪ Nnn, Da-nun ♪"
I just went like that...
Hah....
You're so steesher!
Hiya.
Hi.
Dick.
Well, ladies and gentlemen, that's the end of the show,
but, before you go, I just want to leave you with this thought.
Theist.
Right.
Now, watch this.
The heist.
Think about it, right.
See you later.
SUBBED BY f7cjo PROFESSIONAL AT SLACKING OFF